Preliminary Guide to the John A. Wilson papers, 1974-1993 MS2190
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Subject files, 1974-1993; Series 3
  - Rolodex of business cards [3 of 3], Series 3 (Box 84, Item 3)
  - Ron Cohen's BZA Case 13406, undated; Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Roosevelt Hotel, undated; Series 3 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Rosenthal Condo Moratorium info, undated; Series 3 (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Rothstein and Buckley, undated; Series 3 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - RSVP, undated; Series 3 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - RW Apple, undated; Series 3 (Box 55, Folder 23)
  - RWN Development - 1212 Mass Ave PUD, undated; Series 3 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - S and L Merger, undated; Series 3 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - S.W. Arts Festival, 1988; Series 3 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Samuel Freeman, undated; Series 3 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Scatter Plan, undated; Series 3 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Scatter Plan National Airport, undated; Series 3 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Scatter plan test results reports, undated; Series 3 (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Scattered site public housing, undated; Series 3 (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - Schedule of Heights, undated; Series 3 (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - Scholarship program, undated; Series 3 (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - Schwartz House, undated; Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Schwartz House, undated; Series 3 (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - SE/SW Metro Bus Garage, undated; Series 3 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Seitzman's HMO, undated; Series 3 (Box 45, Folder 21)
  - Sentencing guidelines, undated; Series 3 (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - Shack clinic, undated; Series 3 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Shaw, undated; Series 3 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Shaw - Dupont community center, undated; Series 3 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Shaw - Seventh Commercial Development, undated; Series 3 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Shaw Coalition - redevelopment corporation, undated; Series 3 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Shaw Health Center, undated; Series 3 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Shaw Housing Coalition, undated; Series 3 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Shaw PAC, undated; Series 3 (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - Shaw School Urban Renewal Area - Parcel 40, undated; Series 3 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Shaw School Urban Renewal Areal - Parcel 41, undated; Series 3 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Shaw Urban Renewal, undated; Series 3 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Shaw Urban Renewal - Parcel 19, undated; Series 3 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Shaw Urban Renewal - Parcel 23, undated; Series 3 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Shaw urban renewal - Parcel 23, undated; Series 3 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Shaw/Logan Circle Crime Task Force, undated; Series 3 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Sherry Towers, undated; Series 3 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Shiloh Baptist Church, undated; Series 3 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Shuttle bus service - M 12and14, undated; Series 3 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - SI Communications corporate demo, 1992 August; Series 3 (Box 85, Videocassette 29)
  - Sibley Plaza, undated; Series 3 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Sibley Plaza, undated; Series 3 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Sidewalk cafe legislation, undated; Series 3 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Sidewalk cafes, undated; Series 3 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Sierra Club endorsement, undated; Series 3 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Small Landlord Exemption, 1988; Series 3 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Small Landlord Exemption Emergency Coops, undated; Series 3 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - South Capitol Street, undated; Series 3 (Box 55, Folder 26)
  - South Capitol Street Buzzard Street Study - Dick Westbrook, undated; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - South Capitol Street Development, undated; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Southeast Freeway Playground, undated; Series 3 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Southeast garage, undated; Series 3 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Southwest Citizens Patrol, undated; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Southwest Community House, undated; Series 3 (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - Southwest Mall, undated; Series 3 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Southwest Multi-Purpose Center, undated; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Southwest Neighborhood Assembly, undated; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Southwest Police Station, undated; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Southwest Urban Renewal - Parcel 57-2 (9th and D St.), undated; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Southwest urban renewal leases, undated; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Southwest waterfront festival - problems, undated; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Special events fundraising, undated; Series 3 (Box 59, Folder 20)
  - Speeches, undated; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Sperm Bank Licensure and Regulatory Act, 1985; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Spiel, undated; Series 3 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Spring/Summer Newsletter, 1984; Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Square 317 - Asbury Methodist Church, undated; Series 3 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - St. Elizabeth Hospital, undated; Series 3 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - St. E's Employees certification, undated; Series 3 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - St. John's scholarship program [1/3, undated; Series 3 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - St. John's scholarship program [2/3, undated; Series 3 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - St. John's scholarship program [3/3, undated; Series 3 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - St. Mary's Court, undated; Series 3 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - State Committee Members, 1992-1996; Series 3 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - State hate crimes bills, 1989; Series 3 (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - State Health Planning and Development Agency (SHPDA), undated; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Stationary, undated; Series 3 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Stead Recreation Center, 1989; Series 3 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Story of a People: Expressions in Black, undated; Series 3 (Box 85, Videocassette 28)
  - Street People, undated; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Stuard Marshall Bloch, undated; Series 3 (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - Studio Theatre, undated; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Substance Abuse - Bill 8-77, undated; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Summer Youth Basketball League, undated; Series 3 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Summer Youth Basketball League, undated; Series 3 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Summer/Fall Newsletter, 1986; Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Summer/Fall Newsletter, undated; Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Supplemental Security Income, undated; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Surplus Property, undated; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Surplus Property Res. PR 4-43, undated; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Surplus school property, undated; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Sursam Corda, undated; Series 3 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Sursum Corda, undated; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Sursum Corda - Drugs, 1984; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Sursum Corda Center, undated; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Sursum Corda Neighborhood Center, undated; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Survey Material, undated; Series 3 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - SW Airplane Noise, undated; Series 3 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - SW Brochure/Issues paper, undated; Series 3 (Box 59, Folder 21)
  - SW Community House Fundraiser, 1985 April 27; Series 3 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - SW Crime Issues, undated; Series 3 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - SW House Fundraiser, undated; Series 3 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - SW Mall - Hearing post mortem, undated; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - SW Mall - Task force, 1979; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - SW Mall Building - Occupancy and Permits - Retail Tenants, undated; Series 3 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - SW Mall/Save our Mall Committee, undated; Series 3 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - SW Plan Change Washington Boat Lines, undated; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - SW Urban Renewal - Physician's Offices, undated; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Tags - Low Number - Ward 2, undated; Series 3 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Taiwan Chancery - BZA, undated; Series 3 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - TAP Amendments, 1987; Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - TAP Program, undated; Series 3 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Taxicab Commercial Advertising Act, 1985; Series 3 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Taxicab Commission, undated; Series 3 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Taxicab Commission Information letters and amendments, undated; Series 3 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Taxicab fines, undated; Series 3 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Taylor H. Ralph, undated; Series 3 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Techworld lawsuit, 1986; Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Telephone Rates, 1986; Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Tenant Petition, undated; Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Tenant Purchase Assistance Program WMPHA/Muscle, 1986; Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Tennis fundraiser, 1976 April 10; Series 3 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Testimonial Dinner, 1980 May; Series 3 (Box 58, Folder 25)
  - Testimony and Letters - Linkage, 1988; Series 3 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - The Board Room II, undated; Series 3 (Box 34, Folder 28)
  - The Feldman Case - Exemption from Rent Control, undated; Series 3 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - The Nelson, undated; Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - The Roast, undated; Series 3 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - The Woodward Building, undated; Series 3 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Tort Reform, 1986; Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Tourist buses - Foggy Bottom, undated; Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Tourist home - 1712 Johnson Ave NW, undated; Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Tourist homes in city, 1981; Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Town meetings, undated; Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Townhall meeting - Precint 83, 1976; Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Traffic lights - Georgetown, undated; Series 3 (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - TransAfrica Forum, undated; Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Transcribed sheets, 1980; Series 3 (Box 32, Folder 31)
  - Tribute invitations, undated; Series 3 (Box 37B, Folder 11)
  - Tyler House, undated; Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - UDAGS - Willard Hotel, undated; Series 3 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Uniform conflict of laws, undated; Series 3 (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - Uniform Limited Partnership - United House of Prayer, undated; Series 3 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Uniform Limited Partnership - Urban Philharmonic, undated; Series 3 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Uniform Limited Partnership Act Amendments, 1985; Series 3 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Union Resolutions, undated; Series 3 (Box 51, Folder 21)
  - Unity 1988 DC State Committee Slate, Series 3 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Unity Democrats, undated; Series 3 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Unity Democrats '92, 1992; Series 3 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - University of the District of Columbia - President Green, undated; Series 3 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Unpledged delegates, 1992; Series 3 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Urban Renewal, undated; Series 3 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Urban Renewal - RLA Townhouses - Riggs and S Street NW, undated; Series 3 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Urban Renewal - S.W., undated; Series 3 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Urban Renewal Plans - Misc, undated; Series 3 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - V. Sounitza, undated; Series 3 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Vehicle Cover Req. Act, undated; Series 3 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Vending, undated; Series 3 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Vending, undated; Series 3 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Vending regulations, undated; Series 3 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Victim Rights Act, undated; Series 3 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Victims of Violent Crime Law, undated; Series 3 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Vincent Orange, undated; Series 3 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Virgin Islands investigation, 1984; Series 3 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Volunteer Lists, 1976; Series 3 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Volunteers, undated; Series 3 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Volunteers, 1980; Series 3 (Box 32, Folder 26)
  - Volunteers - labels, 1980; Series 3 (Box 32, Folder 27)
  - Voting instructions, undated; Series 3 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Vouchers, undated; Series 3 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Vouchers, 1983 July 01; Series 3 (Box 37A, Folder 14)
  - Vouchers, undated; Series 3 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Vouchers, undated; Series 3 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Ward 2 Census Information, undated; Series 3 (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Ward 2 Precinct 1, undated; Series 3 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Ward 2 Public Housing Concerns, undated; Series 3 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Ward Plans, 1987; Series 3 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Ward Plans, undated; Series 3 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Ward Plans, undated; Series 3 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Ward Plans, undated; Series 3 (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Ward Plans, undated; Series 3 (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - Ward Plans, undated; Series 3 (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Ward Plans, undated; Series 3 (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - Ward Plans, undated; Series 3 (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - Ward Plans, undated; Series 3 (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - Ward Plans, undated; Series 3 (Box 52, Folder 16)
  - Ward Two Democrats, undated; Series 3 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Ward Two Planning Commnity Advisory Committee, undated; Series 3 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Washington Convention Center, undated; Series 3 (Box 58, Folder 22)
  - Washington, DC, Series 3 (Box 85, Videocassette 5)
  - Washington Post Questionnaire, undated; Series 3 (Box 58, Folder 26)
  - Water and Sewer Ops Amendment, undated; Series 3 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Waterfront Development, undated; Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Waterside Mall hearing, undated; Series 3 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Wax Museum Site, undated; Series 3 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - WD-2 Emergency Food Providers, undated; Series 3 (Box 63, Folder 13)
  - Webster House, undated; Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Welcome Home: The Official Desert Storm Victory Celebration Video, 1991; Series 3 (Box 85, Videocassette 17)
  - Well-Child Care Bill, undated; Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - West End Citizen Association, undated; Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - West End Tenants, undated; Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Westend Tennant Association, undated; Series 3 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Whitehurst Freeway, undated; Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Whitehurst Freeway, undated; Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Whitehurst Freeway, 1989; Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Whitehurst Freeway - Deis, undated; Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Whitehurst Freeway - Draft Deis, undated; Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Whitehurst Freeway - Georgetown, undated; Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Whitehurst Freeway East End Committee, 1985-1986; Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Whitehurst Freeway Foggy Bottom/Westend, undated; Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Whitehurst Freeway Study Commission, undated; Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Whitman-Walker Funding Authorization, undated; Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - John A. Wilson v. Sharon Pratt Dixon, undated; Series 3 (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - John Wilson for City Council -- positions, undated; Series 3 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - John Wilson, Howard University, undated; Series 3 (Box 85, Videocassette 19)
  - John Wilson pilot, 1992 November 16; Series 3 (Box 85, Videocassette 13)
  - John Wilson, University of the District of Columbia presentation, "Black History Month", 1993 February; Series 3 (Box 85, Videocassette 21)
  - Wilson Newsletter, undated; Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Wilson Newsletter - First Draft, 1988; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Wilson Newsletter - Original Materials, 1988; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - The Wilson Plan, 1988; Series 3 (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Wilson recall, 1993; Series 3 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Wilson Report, 1980 November; Series 3 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Wilson Report, 1984 April; Series 3 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Wilson Report, 1983; Series 3 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Wilson Report, undated; Series 3 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Wilson Reports, undated; Series 3 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Wilson Ward Two Low Tag File, undated; Series 3 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Winter Plaza - Parcel 7, undated; Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Wisconsin Avenue Corridor Committee, undated; Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Wisconsin Avenue Zoning, undated; Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Wisteria Mansion, undated; Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Woodland - Normanstone Overlay, undated; Series 3 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Work Papers, 03/1988 - 06/1988; Series 3 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Workers Compensation, undated; Series 3 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Workers' Compensation, 1979-1980; Series 3 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Workmen's Compensation, undated; Series 3 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Workmen's Compensation, undated; Series 3 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Workmen's Compensation, undated; Series 3 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - WPA Relocation, undated; Series 3 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Xeroxed checks, 1988 January 31; Series 3 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Xeroxed checks - contributions, 1987 July 31; Series 3 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - YMCA, undated; Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - YMCA, undated; Series 3 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Young Investors -- Amidon Elementary School, undated; Series 3 (Box 85, Videocassette 2)
  - Youth Rehabilitation Act, 1985; Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Yuen Corporation et al v. City Councilmembers, undated; Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Zenith Gallery, undated; Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Zone Study Commission, undated; Series 3 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Zoning - Corcoran Street and New Hampshire NW, undated; Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Zoning - DuPont Circle, undated; Series 3 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Zoning - Home offices and bed and breakfasts, undated; Series 3 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Zoning - Non conforming uses, undated; Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Zoning - Special Exceptions, undated; Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Zoning - SW Urban Renewal Area Final Report, undated; Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Zoning Adjustment Board - Winthrop House, undated; Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Zoning Case 786P American Trucking Association, undated; Series 3 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Zoning case 79-1 (hotels), undated; Series 3 (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - Zoning Case 79-15P Fairlawn Development, undated; Series 3 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Zoning Case 79-2 PUD Regs, undated; Series 3 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Zoning Case 80-7 Consolidation PUD and Air Space, undated; Series 3 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Zoning Case 81-10 Greenleaf, undated; Series 3 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Zoning Case 86-32C 26th and L St [1of 2, undated; Series 3 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Zoning Case 86-32C 26th and L St [2of 2, undated; Series 3 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Zoning Case 87-19C Hadid Project, undated; Series 3 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Zoning Case 88-11C and 88-12C, undated; Series 3 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Zoning Case 88-8C - Potomac Development Corp, undated; Series 3 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Zoning Case 89-20C 23rd and N St. NW, undated; Series 3 (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Zoning Commission, undated; Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Zoning Commission - World Bank/Foggy Bottom, undated; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Zoning commission appointment, undated; Series 3 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Zoning Commission Case 86-32C - 26th and L NW, undated; Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Zoning enforcement, undated; Series 3 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Zoning Square 121, undated; Series 3 (Box 20, Folder 7)